Gera Jahja

About me

I am currently working as a Software Engineering at Vodafone in their future comms team. My current interests are in programming and software development. I have experience in Java, Vb.net, python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C++ and more. Independent projects I've taken part in have usually been related to programming solutions that are research based.

Recent Project:

Decompiling EVM bytecode to C

https://github.com/kristielGJ/DecompilingEVMtoC

Academic proposal supervised by Martin Nyx Brain and Michał Król. The project is a decompiler that converts EVM byte code (Ethereum byte code) into C which can be handled by CPROVER tools. This could enable us to identify hidden bugs in EVM code such as Solidity programs.

Education

City University of London: Computer science BSc Hons (2019-2022)

Grade: First Class 1:1

Woodhouse College: A level: (2017 - 2019)

Grades: 128 UCAS Points

(Art, Computer science, Psychology, Maths) Enfield County School GCSE (2012 - 2017)

Grades: A*- B (8-6)

(Maths, English, Science, Additional Science, Computer Science, Sociology, Art, Spanish)

References:

(Written references are available upon request)

Martin Nyx Brain -Lecturer at City University of London: Email: martin.brain@city.ac.uk

Marie-Christine Beesoon -Human Resources at Artificial: Tel. 020 3880 8461 / christine@artificial.io

Friederike Brandt - Head of European Operations at Freepoint Commodities Europe LLP

Ph: 0044 20 3262 6410 / Mob: 0044 7780 472 113/ Email: fbrandt@freepoint.com

Phone: +44 7983 584309_____ Email: g_jahja31@outlook.com

Work Experience

https://www.linkedin.com/in/gerajahja/

Vodafone: Software Engineer

Kingdom Street, Paddington, London (September 2022- Current)

Working In Future Comms developing innovative products for Vodafone Group. Working using Golang for backend development and React/ Typescript for front end.

Learn2Code.live: Programming Instructor

Based in America (Feb 2021 – August 2022)

Courses include Python, Scratch, Web design & development, and AI courses using Python, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Java, C++; and game design & development.

Code Ninjas: Lead Coding Instructor Enfield, London (June 2021 – Feb 2022)

Lead Code sensei, teaching in-person: Game-based curriculum that introduces children to programming. Hosted camps over half term such as Roblox game development etc.

Artificial: Engineering Work Experience

Bow Lane, London (July 2019)

Programmed in PHP (OOP, correcting by construction, added validation to existing code etc.) Gained experience in using GitHub via a console, running tests using phpUnit, Docker Programmed in Haskell (functional programming), the coding tasks was based on tasks I did in PHP

Salesforce : Work Experience

Liverpool street, London (Dates: 9th -13th of April 2018)

Worked with the marketing cloud team, the marketing cloud sales team as well as the core sales team, marketing cloud business development team, solution engineer, and the marketing team.

Vodafone: Group Work Experience

Kingdom street, Paddington, London (February 2018)

Learnt and produced presentations with three to four colleagues in the following fields: - HR (Learning and Development) - Technology (System Architecture) - Commercial Marketing

```
{
          'Digital Marketing': ['Digital Marketing', 'SEO', 'SEM', 'Content Marketing', 'Email Marketing'],
          'Data Analysis': ['Data Analysis', 'Data Visualization', 'Data Mining', 'Statistical Analysis'],
          'Business Analysis': ['Business Analysis', 'Requirement Gathering', 'Process Modeling', 'SWOT
Analysis'],
          'Software Development': ['Software Development', 'Programming', 'Agile Methodology', 'Version
Control'],
          'Project Management': ['Project Management', 'Risk Management', 'Stakeholder Management',
'Agile Project Management'],
          'Cloud Computing': ['Cloud Computing', 'AWS', 'Azure', 'Google Cloud Platform', 'DevOps'],
          'UX Design': ['User Experience (UX) Design', 'Wireframing', 'Prototyping', 'Usability Testing'],
          'AI/ML': ['Artificial Intelligence (AI)', 'Machine Learning (ML)', 'Deep Learning', 'Natural Language
Processing'l.
          'Sales': ['Sales', 'Negotiation', 'Client Relationship Management', 'Lead Generation'],
          'Marketing': ['Marketing', 'Brand Management', 'Market Research', 'Advertising'],
          'Languages': ['Languages', 'Fluent in English', 'Spanish Proficiency', 'French (Basic)'],
       }
```